I don't get frustrated at my own failings.
That kind of thing never has been,
and never will be, a part of my life.
I simply confront the evils
that force this reality upon us.
And I will.
Arrogant bastards.
You are my special.
You
are
my special.
You are my special.
Now I'm not sure how to go.
I don't want you to be able to do it.
I don't want you to be able to.
I should make you cry,
you're a little devil.
I make it so much you are my special.
I don't want you to be able to do it.
I should make you cry,
you're a little devil. You
are
aware
of my technique,
aren't you?
I have the ability to control crows.
That's it.
Sounds weak, huh?
That's why I trained so
diligently ever since I was young.
I wanted to be able to
fight without my technique.
It wasn't a waste of my time.
Being able to overwhelm
you like this proves it.
Stop!
I'll pull out of this right now!
I swear I will!
Somebody spare me!
You're interrupting my sister,
and she's not finished talking.
I used to tell myself that a sorcerer's
true value wasn't their technique.
But eventually, I hit my limit.
I couldn't keep improving
my physical abilities
and enhancing myself with
cursed energy forever.
I was crushed.
I had lost heart.
So I decided to embrace and
master my own technique.
And that's when I came into full
bloom as a grade one sorcerer.
Applause.
No, I'll kill you.
I just wanted to kill some
time chatting for a while.
Promise, I'm sorry!
I won't be bad again!
Please!
Please spare my life!
Hey, Wee Wee.
Tell me something.
How do you suppose one measures the
weight and value of a single life?
That's easy!
It all depends how valuable
that life is to you, big sister!
Thank you and you i uh well i guess
You can't immediately
describe the scale you use to
measure the lives you hunt
down That's the reason why you
lost and just so you know what
i think about it I measure
lives by their service
potential that's what matters
Huh?
How come only the veil that was
keeping sorcerers out got lifted?
They all should have lifted since we
just broke three of these with Eno.
Either they used all three to lower
one veil, or two of them were dummies.
Regardless, sorcerers can
move freely in Shibuya now.
That just leaves the veil
that's trapping Gojo,
and the veil that's
trapping ordinary people.
I wanted to ask this geezer more
questions, but he won't wake up.
We should rejoin Eno.
Eno!
The veil's lifted.
What now, Granny?
What if we do now?
It won't hurt to keep Satoru Gojo out of
play for a while longer, so go down there!
and kill as many sorcerers as you find.
Ransun?
Who the hell do you think
you're ordering around, Hag?
What's the meaning of this?
I only channeled the body's
information, not the soul's.
...channeled.
Ah, now I get it.
This can't be.
I've always made it a point
not to channel the soul
in order to prevent accidents
like this ahead of time.
I'm not sure exactly why, but
my body has always been special.
I guess that's why your grandson's
soul lost against my body.
A soul losing to a body?
No!
That's impossible!
Kill sorcerers, huh?
You're a sorcerer.
They really hit Ijichi?
It sounded like he got attacked
while on the phone with Nita.
So it probably happened after
he left Fushiguro's group.
He might be in trouble.
Nobara, go with Akari to Ijichi.
We can't use our cell phones in here,
so we won't get anywhere without
the assistant supervisors.
I doubt that idiot Satoru would ever lose,
but this whole situation
is smelling even fishier.
I'll take care of things here for now.
That old man is completely useless.
Ignore him.
Now go!
Right!
Worst case scenario, once they're
outside the Veil, they can run.
How is he?
He's not doing well.
But he's not dead.
I'm gonna knock them out! He's a dory.
I understand how you feel, alright?
But what's our highest priority right now?
Rescuing Gojo.
The Veil's been lifted.
The people at the top might
have escaped already anyway.
Anyway, I'll take Eno with
me and head outside the veil.
Okay, you take care of Eno.
I'll go on ahead to the station.
I agree, that's the best course.
But operating alone in
Shibuya right now is not...
Alright, good. But if you... I know.
If I die, you'll kill me.
Am I right?
Don't worry so much.
I have Mechamaru with me.
Though, I haven't heard anything
from him for a while now.
Just as long as you understand.
See you later.
Yeah!
Fix this.
Looks like the veil is gone.
Oh boy.
The thought of how much I'll get for
making Satoru Gojo owe me a favor.
It just makes my heart raise.
That was faster than expected.
Nita, stop!
Oh, it's a woman in a suit!
Oh, I'm so happy.
I was getting sick of them all being men.
Nita, you better go hide.
I'm gonna finish this quickly.
In fact, pretend to hide in Bunkamura,
then keep going and slip through Tokyo.
From the way he's talking, he
probably took out Eiji-chi,
which means we need to hurry.
Right.
Kugisaki, don't push yourself too hard.
Whispering to each other?
Now you've got me curious!
Aww!
Aww, she's going to hide.
Whoa!
You must be throwing the match
if you're coming at me unarmed.
Didn't I meet you before?
Most who rely on cursed tools
are mid - or long-range fighters,
so keep up the attack.
Remind me who you are again!
Shooting nails is dangerous, you know.
Oh, I'll make it even
more dangerous for you.
Hey.
So she wasn't hiding after all.
Nika!
He shoots!
Scores!
Why, you...
The sword he dropped earlier...
Where did it come from?
Uh…
Huh…
Hiya!
Too bad!
Hairpin!
Nita!
Yeah, you really are
dangerous, aren't you?
Aw, did it hit your chin?
Hey, can't you stand?
Hello? You there?
Gotta say, you've gotten an awful
lot stronger since we last met.
I didn't even recognize you at first.
But being strong isn't enough
to win in this world, you know.
Especially when my technique is involved.
Although, believe it or not,
I don't really understand my
own technique all that well.
Now then, which of you
should I kill first?
What?
Huh?
Work, mouth work!
What are you after?
Buy as much time as possible!
Uh, they said something about
wanting to seal Satoru Gojo.
I was asking you what you want.
Oh, really?
What do you think someone with
a great talent and love for
soccer would do if they were
born in a world without soccer?
No, that's not right.
I can't explain it well.
Although, is the reason
really that important?
I mean, who cares?
The whole thing's fun, right?
As long as I keep having fun,
what else really matters?
Wouldn't you agree, Leia?
Cut it out!
Oh, ow!
Please, don't let me commit any.
Oh, I'm full of fun.
Watch where you step!
Yeah, yeah!
Ooh, look at this.
I get to kill people that
aren't in black suits.
He must have come to
Shibuya with Fushiguro.
Nanami.
Come on now, man.
Just look around you.
You really sure you want to approach me?
I mean, can't you see I'm
holding a woman hush-skitch here?
Huh?
She ran away.
How many are there?
Allies and their locations.
I don't know.
A wall?
I didn't cut him?
Not a scratch.
Number and locations of your allies.
Now!
Huh? Did I die?
No, but I would have died
without my technique.
I...
I have to run!
The number of your allies
and their locations.
I told you, I don't know!
Nope, not this time.
Hey, you weren't invited.
On my way here, I found several
of our assistant supervisors dead.
That was you, right?
I'm sorry.
He's on another level.
This is what it means to
be a grade one sorcerer.
Come on, let's make our way to Nita.
Well, well, well, it's you.
Mei Mei, it's been too long.
Quite the thing to say after
sending an assassin after me, Code.
How is he alive?
Did Gojo screw up last year?
Unless Gojo and Code were in on
this whole commotion together.
No, definitely not.
Gojo could kill every person in this
country all on his own if he wanted to.
There'd be no need or point in setting up
these tricks or getting
anyone else involved.
I actually held you in higher
regard than Gojo, you know.
That nihilistic smile of yours
was always quite charming.
It's a shame that I'll
have to kill you now.
And squash such potential.
It's quite a shame.
Genuinely.
This Code has got to be a fake.
Mei Mei.
I think it's a shame too.
To think I'd have to go after
my former upperclassmen.
First manipulation.
Did I read this wrong?
This is a special grade
disease curse. Smallpox deity.
I used up my stock of cursed
spirits by the end of last year.
But this is of good quality.
Just to be safe, I want to keep
the humans on the B5 level.
I'll wait down this line.
If you succeed here,
I'll take you on next.
Domain expansion this is going
to be a little troublesome.
I've been trapped I'm
inside a coffin I suppose
Big Sis!
Three, two...
Well, how many years has it been since
something has threatened my life like this?
Big Sis!
There's absolutely no one here.
I thought there was supposed to be a
huge crowd trapped inside the station.
So, you're saying Ichichi is okay?
I did all I could to save
him for the time being.
And don't forget he had once trained
to become a sorcerer himself.
Anyway, it seems that none of your group
had heard about Gojo's situation yet.
We entered the building right
away as soon as we arrived.
That's probably why.
He's still holding out after being sealed.
That's so like him.
I want you two to wait
here for the rescue team.
I'll join Zenin and we'll head down to B5.
I'm going to...
No, you're not.
Grade 1 is the minimum level
required for the fights ahead.
You would only get in the way.
Please, just wait here.
Yuji Itadori, I will avenge my brothers!
The one who said something
was I'd never forget.
What I'd be saying was I'd
be able to say something.
I'd be able to say something.
I'd be able to choose the right way.
I'm sure that the pain will be the same.
The night will be you.
Just be by yourself.
I'm giving more than once.
Egg, I'll help you with work.
It's fine, I'm fine.
Oh, don't be shy, we're Gen Z.
Excel, PowerPoint, we're
pros at this stuff.
I mean it, I'm really fine.
Next time, red scale.
What does merge cells mean?
Do it, do it.
Seriously, go away!